Well, the first observation is that both equations give us the same line.
第一个观点是两个方程给我们相同的直线
The line with equation x_1 plus x_2 equals zero.
这条直线方程是 X1 + X2 = 0
And the reason for this is that solution two
原因在于第二个解法
is really just a scalar multiple of solution one.
实际上只是第一个解法的纯量倍数
So let's see. Recall that the prediction is a sigmoid of the linear function.
那么我们来看一下 回想一下 预测是一个 sigmoid 线性函数
So in the first case, for the point 1, 1,
所以在第一个例子中 对于点 (1,1)
it would be sigmoid of one plus one,
可以是 sigmoid (1+1)
which is sigmoid of two, which is 0.88.
即 sigmoid 2 等于 0.88
This is not bad since the point is blue so it has a label of one.
因为这个点是蓝色的 所以结果不算差 所以标签为 1
For the point -1, -1, the prediction is sigmoid of -1 plus -1,
对于点 (-1,-1) 预测是 sigmoid (-1-1)
which is sigmoid of -2, which is 0.12.
即 sigmoid -2 等于 0.12
This is also not bad since the point has a label of zero since it's red.
因为这个点标签为 0 是红色的 所以结果不算差
Now, let's see what happens with the second model.
我们来看一下第二个模型
The point 1,1, has a prediction sigmoid of 10 times one plus 10 times one,
点 (1,1) 预测结果是 sigmoid (10+10)
which is sigmoid of 20.
即 sigmoid 20
This is 0.9999999979, which is really close to 1,
结果为 0.9999999979 非常接近 1
so it's a great prediction.
所以这是个很好的预测
And the point -1, -1,
对于点 (-1,-1)
has prediction sigmoid of 10 times -1 plus 10 times -1,
预测结果是 sigmoid (-10-10)
which is sigmoid of -20,
即 sigmoid -20
and that is 0.0000000021.
等于 0.0000000021
That's really, really close to zero,
这非常接近 0
so it's a great prediction.
所以这是个很好的预测
So the answer to the quiz is the second model.
所以这个测试的答案是第二个模型
The second model is super accurate.
第二个模型非常准确
This means it's better, right?
也意味着更好
Well, after the last section,
在最后一部分
you may be a bit reluctant since this hints a bit towards overfitting.
因为这可能有点过度拟合 所以你觉得有点勉强
And your hunch is correct.
而且你的预感是正确的
The problem is overfitting but in a subtle way.
这个问题有点过度拟合
Here's what's happening and here's why the first model is better,
这是整个过程 以及第一个模型更好的原因
even if it gives a larger error.
即使得出更大的误差
When we apply sigmoid to small values such as x_1 plus x_2,
我们把 sigmoid 运用到较小值中 如 X1 + X2
we get the function on the left,
我们得到左侧的函数
which has a nice slope to the gradient descent.
包含梯度下降法的较好斜率
When we multiply the linear function by 10 and take sigmoid of 10_x_1 plus 10_x_2,
我们把线性函数乘以 10 后得到 sigmoid (10X1+10X2)
our predictions are much better since they're closer to zero and one,
由于结果更趋近于 0 和 1 所以预测更好一些
but the function becomes much steeper and it's much harder to do
但是函数更加陡峭 这里也更难使用
gradient descent here since the derivatives are mostly close to zero,
梯度下降法 因为导数几乎接近 0
and they're very large when we get to the middle of the curve.
到达曲线中部时 导数非常大
Therefore, in order to do gradient descent properly,
所以 为了合理使用梯度下降法
we want a model like the one in the left more than a model like the one in the right.
相比右侧的模型来说 我们更想用左侧的模型
In a conceptual way,
从概念上来说
the model in the right is too certain,
右侧的模型非常稳定
and it gives little room for applying gradient descent.
很难应用梯度下降法
Also, as we can imagine,
同时正如我们想象到的
the points that are classified incorrectly in the model
这些点在右侧模型中分类错误
in the right will generate large errors,
会导致更大的偏差
and it would be hard to tune the model to correct them.
这样会很难调优模型或纠正模型
These can be summarized in the quote by the famous philosopher
这可以引用著名哲学家和数学家伯特兰·罗素
and mathematician, Bertrand Russell.
的名言进行总结
The whole problem with
人工智能的问题
artificial intelligence is that bad models are so certain of themselves,
在于错误模型对自身非常确定
and good models are so full of doubts.
而好的模型充满疑问
Now the question is,
现在问题是
how do we prevent this type of overfitting from happening?
我们如何避免这种过度拟合的发生呢？
This seems to not be easy since the bad model gives smaller errors.
由于错误模型提供了更小误差 所以这并不简单
Well, all we have to do is we have to tweak the error function a bit.
我们要做的是对误差函数稍作调整
Basically, we want to punish high coefficients.
大体来说 我们想要惩罚高系数
So what we do is we take the old error function and add a term,
那么我们要做的是 利用原来的误差函数 增加一项
which is big when the weights are big.
如果权重大 那么这项也大
There are two ways to do this.
两种方法可以做到这些
One way is to add the sums of absolute values of the weights
第一种方法是加上权重绝对值的总和
times a constant lambda.
再乘以常数 λ
The other one is to add the sum of the squares of the weights times that same constant.
另一种方法是加上权重平方总和 再乘以相同的常数
As you can see, these two are large if the weights are large.
可以看到 如果权重大 这两个函数都大
The lambda parameter will tell us how much we want to penalize the coefficients.
参数 λ 告诉我们惩罚系数的多少
If lambda is large,
如果 λ 很大
we penalize them a lot,
会惩罚很严重
and if Lambda is small,
如果 λ 很小
then we don't penalize them much.
那么不需要惩罚很严重
And finally, if we decide to go for the absolute values,
最后如果我们想要得到绝对值
we're doing L1 regularization.
可以使用 L1 正则化
And if we decide to go for the squares,
如果想要得到平方
then we're doing L2 regularization.
可以使用 L2 正则化
Both are very popular,
两者都比较通用
and depending on our goals,
取决于我们的目标
our application will be applying one or the other.
我们可以应用其中一个或另一个
Here are some general guidelines for deciding between L1 and L2 regularization.
对于使用 L1 和 L2 正则化 这里有一些通用规则
When we apply L1, we tend to end up with sparse vectors.
使用 L1 正则化时 我们希望得到稀疏向量
That means small weights will tend to go to zero.
它表示较小权重趋向于 0
So if you want to reduce the number of weights and end up with a small set,
所以如果你想降低权重值 最终得到较小的数
we can use L1.
我们可以使用 L1
This is also good for feature selections since sometimes,
这也利于特征选择 因为有时候
we have a problem with hundreds of features and
我们会遇到几百种特征问题
L1 regularization will help us select which ones are important.
L1 正则化可以帮我们选择哪一些更重要
And it will turn the rest into zeroes.
然后将其余的变为 0
L2, on the other hand,
而 L2 正则化
tends not to favor sparse vectors since it tries
不支持稀疏向量
to maintain all the weights homogeneously small.
因为它确保所有权重一致较小
This one normally gives better results for training models so
这个一般可以训练模型 得出更好结果
it's the one we'll use the most. Now, let's think a bit.
所以这会是我们最常用的 现在我们来想一下
Why would L1 regularization produce vectors with sparse weights and
为什么 L1 正则化得出稀疏权重的向量
L2 regularization will produce vectors with small homogeneous weights?
而 L2 正则化得出较小齐权的向量？
Well, here's an idea of why.
原因是这样的
If we take the vector 1, 0,
如果我们向量 (1,0)
the sums of the absolute values of the weights are one,
权重绝对值的总和是 1
and the sums of the squares of the weights are also one.
权重平方的总和也是 1
But if we take the vector 0.5, 0.5,
如果得到向量 (0.5, 0.5)
the sums of the absolute values of the weights is still one,
权重绝对值的总和仍然是 1
but the sums of the squares is 0.25 plus 0.25, which is 0.5.
平方总和是 0.25 加 0.25 等于 0.5
Thus, L2 regularization will prefer the vector 0.5,
那么 L2 正则化更倾向于向量 (0.5, 0.5)
0.5, over the vector 1,
而不是向量 (1,0)
0, since this one produces a smaller sum of squares and in turn,
因为前者可以得出更小的平方总和
a smaller error function.
以及更小的误差函数